SASCHA ANDEWEG

LINGUISTIC DATA ANALYST / FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER /

Working in the printing business in The Netherlands has made me passionate about creating bespoke products for clients that I built long lasting working relationships with. Those 28 years of developing ideas, designing and producing material for print and web have given me great joy and priceless experience. After moving to Ireland with my family in 2016 a total career change gave me a boost in many ways. I was able to use my experience working in machine learning for a multinational. This has given me the confidence that after my recent graduation from the Code Institute and getting a level 6 diploma in **Full Stack Software Development** I can continue following my passion for developing, creating and exceeding client's expectations.

CONTACT

20 Hawthorn Crescent Forest Glen, P61K253 Fermoy, Co. Cork T: 089 7028 790 E: sascha@designed.irish

(SOCIAL) MEDIA

- LinkedIn
- Portfolio

HOBBIES/INTERESTS

- Improvised music
- Photography
- Graphic Design
- · The power of language

REFERENCES

Emma Flynn

HR Manager Globetech Ltd. **T:** 21 4839380 **E:** emma.flynn@globetech.ie

Adri Bareman

CEO TekstBeeld Groep T: +31 115 613072 E: a.bareman@tekstbeeld.nl

Ronny Rammeloo

Rammeloo Communications T: +31 117 453467 E: ryro@zeelandnet.nl

EXPERIENCE

2016 - present GLOBETECH LTD.

Linguistic Grader/Curator

Linguistic analysis for machine learning. Due to a non-disclosure contract I cannot share further details about the position.

1985 - 2016

DRUKKERIJ BAREMAN / TEKSTBEELD GROEP

Prepress specialist / Graphic Designer

From the early days of phototype setting to digital printing and webdesign I have been part of the evolution of the printing industry into a largely digitalised media business.

2006 - 2016

RAMMELOO COMMUNICATIONS

Graphic Designer

As freelancer I produced the layout of a local paper and created presentation material.

VOLUNTEERING

- present

As a member of a religious organization I help scheduling and managing the exchange of weekly public talks between congregations and participate also as a public speaker.

SKILLS

Data Analysis

Graphic Design

Junior Full Stack Software Developer

Trained in:

HTML • CSS • Bootstrap • JavaScript • test driven development (Jasmine) • using API's • JQuery • Python • Flask • MySQL • MongoDB • Postgres • Django • Git

EDUCATION

2019 - 2020

FULL STACK WEBDEVELOPER

CodeInstitute, Dublin, Ireland

2011

WORKSHOP COLUMN WRITING

Marjon Sarneel, The Netherlands

2010

TRAINING 'EXPERT IN SALES'

Kenneth Smit, The Netherlands

1000

DREAMWEAVER/FLASH COURSE

GOC, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

1008

BASIC WEBDESIGN AND HTML

GOC, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

1990-1991

GRAPHIC TECHNICIAN PREPRESS

GOC, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

1988-1990

BASIC PREPRESS

 $\underline{\mathsf{GOC}}$, Rotterdam, The Netherlands

1985

NHI, Terneuzen, The Netherlands

1985-1988

LEAVING CERT

Zwin College, Oostburg, The Netherlands